module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'How many periods are in an ice hockey game?', 
    a: 'One',
    b: 'Two',
    c: 'Three',
    d: 'Four',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What instrument has a long neck bearing frets and a pear-shaped body?', 
    a: 'Uncello',
    b: 'Yabahar',
    c: 'Theremin',
    d: 'Lute',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is George Alan O\'Dowd famously known as?', 
    a: 'Boy George',
    b: 'George Michael',
    c: 'George Clooney',
    d: 'George R.R. Martin',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'The furcula is another name for which bone?', 
    a: 'Femur',
    b: 'Wishbone ',
    c: 'Talus',
    d: 'Tibia',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What type of dainty cookies are used often in a tiramisu cake?', 
    a: 'Ladyfingers',
    b: 'Biscoti',
    c: 'Amaretti',
    d: 'Shortbread',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Braeburn, Rome & Gravenstein are varieties of what?', 
    a: 'Apples',
    b: 'Pears',
    c: 'Flowers',
    d: 'Squash',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'During their 1983 tour, the Red Hot Chili Peppers famously wore which article of clothing in an untraditional manner?', 
    a: 'Hoodies',
    b: 'Underwear',
    c: 'Hats',
    d: 'Socks',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these people is the richest (in net worth)?', 
    a: 'Bill Gates',
    b: 'Warren Buffett',
    c: 'Jeff Bezos',
    d: 'Mark Zuckerberg',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which Disney film was released in 1981?', 
    a: 'The Fox and the Hound',
    b: 'The Jungle Book',
    c: 'The Black Cauldron',
    d: 'The Little Mermaid',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following foods would an aardvark find most appetizing?', 
    a: 'Ants',
    b: 'Grass',
    c: 'Grubs',
    d: 'Seeds',
    answer: 'a'
  },
];
